The sprint is something that you need to design and
冲刺需要提前设计
it's the job of the sprint master or you in this case, to plan the activities
冲刺总管或者是你需要提前计划
that you're going to do before, during and after the sprint.
在冲刺之前、冲刺期间以及冲刺之后需要做什么
Let me give you an idea of what you can expect in each of these periods.
现在我简单告诉你不同时期应该做什么
First, you should know that you're going to do a lot of work up front.
首先 你要知道你需要提前做很多工作
In general, you want to spend about one day of planning for
总体来说 你需要花费一天时间
each day of the design sprint.
为设计冲刺的每一天制定计划
Now this will feel like a lot of work and it should be.
听上去好像很多工作 实际上也应该是这样
The good news is that good planning will help you run a smooth design sprint and
好消息是 好的计划会让设计冲刺更加流畅
let you solve your design challenge quickly.
让你能快速解决你的设计挑战
Before the design sprint, you'll want to write a design brief.
在设计冲刺之前 你需要写一份设计概要
This will let you define your design challenge and
通过它 你可以确认你的设计挑战
then it will also let you set a timeline for when you want to launch or when you
以及制定时间线 确定你想要发布产品
want this deliverable, whatever it is in the design sprint to be reviewed.
或得到成品的时间 或者是设计冲刺期间进行回顾的时间
Before the sprint, you'll also want to invite team members or
在冲刺之前 你还需要邀请团队成员
talent to the sprint.
或其他人才加入冲刺
Nadia will talk more about this later and
Nadia 之后会谈论更多相关内容
one of the key parts of a design sprint is user testing.
设计冲刺的关键部分之一是用户测试
You need to schedule when users will take a look at whatever you design from
针对在设计冲刺期间什么时间让用户测试你的产品
the design sprint.
你需要制定计划
The user testing will keep you accountable, validate product ideas and
用户测试会让你更加负责任 帮助你确认产品创意
push you and perhaps your team toward showing users something by
并推动你和你的团队在设计冲刺的最后阶段
the end of the design sprint.
向用户展示东西
Now this might now make a whole lot of sense right now,
可能现在你还不明白这个的整体意义
but I guarantee you it will by the end of this lesson.
但我保证到了这课的最后你就明白了
Finally, before the sprint, you'll also want to schedule any lightning talks
最后 在冲刺之前 你需要安排更多的闪电式演讲
more on this later and you want to prep the slide deck
然后准备冲刺阶段需要使用的幻灯片
that you'll use in the sprint and leave room for special materials.
并留下空间加入特殊材料
In the next video, I'll cover the details of a design brief and
在下一个视频中 我会具体说明设计概要
how you can appropriately scope your design challenge.
以及你要如何恰当地确认设计挑战的范围
Here are the tasks that you'll need to do during a design sprint.
这些是你在设计冲刺期间需要完成的任务
If you're working alone, you won't need to do daily check ins and
如果你单独工作 你就不需要做每日检查
daily summaries, instead you should keep a master list of all the tasks you
和每日摘要 你只需要列一个你需要完成的所有任务的清单
need to get done, so that way you can stay organized.
这样你会更加有条理
You should also write reflections after each day, so you can look back on them
你还应在每天结束时写下你的相关思考 这样你回头看时
and get better at planning and designing the sprints alone or with a team.
可能方便你更好地计划和设计冲刺 无论你是独自工作或是和团队合作
One of the hardest parts about conducting a design sprint
而设计冲刺中最艰难的部分
is facilitating conversation and
是推动对话
resolving conflict among your teammates should they arise.
以及解决团队成员之间可能出现的矛盾
Now you won't really need to worry about this if you're working alone, but
如果你是单独工作 那你还不需要烦这个问题
you will need to be the point person or
但你需要作为负责人
appoint someone else to resolve any conflicts when they do arise.
或指点其他人负责任何出现的矛盾
After the design sprint, you should take the lead to summarize the results and
在设计冲刺之后 你需要带头总结冲刺结果
plan next steps.
并计划下一步
If you worked with a team, you'll want to send out a short survey to ask your
如果你是与团队合作 你需要发送较短的调查
teammates about how the design sprint went and what could go better next time.
询问团队成员设计冲刺进行得怎样 以及下一次该怎么改进
If you're working solo, then you should just reflect on what happened and
如果你独自工作 你就应该回想发生过的事
how you might improve in the future.
以及未来如何改进
And hopefully,
最理想的是
you're already working towards planning your next design sprint.
你已经在为下一次设计冲刺做计划了
All of this should feel like a lot of work and well, it is.
感觉上工作量很大 实际上也是这样
Thankfully, many other companies have done design sprints before and
幸好 很多其他公司之前已经完成过设计冲刺
there's tons of great resources and documentation and
然后有很多关于如何进行设计冲刺的
short articles about how to conduct design sprints.
资源、文件、短文
Global Ventures, for example,
比如说 Global Ventures
has put together this awesome list of resources for you.
它集合了所有的资源清单
They also have a great collection, a library of resources that has short
你还能看到庞大的资源库
articles that will walk you through all of the steps needed to schedule and
里面的短文会帮助你安排所有的步骤
conduct user research interviews.
并进行用户研究的面谈
These are also the your usability testing interviews
这里还有你在设计冲刺的最后会做的
that you'll do at the end of a design sprint.
可用性测试面谈
All of these resources will be included in a reading node at the end of this
所有的这些资源你都可以在本课最后的
lesson.
扩展阅读中找到
They also have a great library of additional resources.
另外你还能看到很多其他的资源
In this library, you'll find a collection of short articles that will
在这个资源库中有很多帮助你安排所有需要的步骤
walk you through all the steps needed to schedule and conduct user research and
进行用户研究和可用性面谈的短文
usability interviews, The links to these articles will be provided in a reading
这些文章的链接 请参见本课最后的
node at the end of this lesson.
扩展阅读